This is Mr Friday.
He has come to The SCOAN with the problem of anus cancer.
This terrible disease has made it virtually impossible for him to sit, walk, or even sleep.
One can only imagine the excruciating pain that is caused by the cancer
protruding from the anus.
INCREDIBLE!!! Anus Cancer PROTRUDING From Man's Body VANISHES After Prayer!
My name is Mr Friday Igbaifua.
I have anus cancer.
I am 35 years old from Edo State.
Where have you been to in search of solution to this problem of anus cancer?
They have been taking me to herbalists to take herbal drugs.
I then said that all those herbal drugs could not work or cure this problem;
it is better I went to a church or I look for another solution.
That was how I came to The SCOAN today.
How has this problem of anus cancer affected your life?
What are the things you cannot do as a result of this problem?
I cannot walk, stand or even sleep ever since I have had this problem.
I have been in pain. As I am standing here right now, it is not me that is standing here
except I lie down.
I believe as I came to The SCOAN, I am going to be healed by God's grace.
Amen. We believe with you that God Almighty will heal you and set you free
from this problem of anus cancer, in Jesus' name.
Amen.
You can see the discomfort on Mr Friday's face.
Again, he shows the severity of his condition.
But he has come to The SCOAN, believing that Jesus Christ, the Master Healer,
would set him totally free.
HEALING TIME
Man of God, please have mercy on me.
Man of God, pray for me.
I cannot sleep.
Viewers all over the world, I want you to see what I am looking at.
He is a human being just like you.
And I believe that by looking at it, you give thanks to God
for what God is doing in your life.
And I know with your prayer, glory would be for God
and the man would be relieved in the name of Jesus.
Healing In Jesus' Name
In Jesus Christ's name.
Come on!
Healing In Jesus' Name
In Jesus' name.
You are free.
So, you are free.
A few days later, Mr Friday came back to testify to his miraculous healing from anus cancer.
Let's listen to him.
Before and After
Brother, can you tab your buttocks?
Tap it very well.
How are you feeling right now?
I'm not feeling any pain anymore.
Tap it again.
How do you feel?
I couldn't tap or touch it like this before. But now I can.
How do you feel now?
Everything is gone, it is healed.
You are free.
I am free.
No more pain.
But before now, were you able to tap it like this?
Before, I couldn't even touch it, not to talk of tapping it.
Now I can do everything.
To God be the glory.
Yes, Mr Friday is totally healed after receiving prayer from Prophet T. B. Joshua in Jesus' name.
There is not a problem He can't solve and not a sickness He can't heal.
Glory be to God.
Now I am free, I give thanks to Jesus Christ.
I am free. I am healed. Thank You, Jesus.
TESTIMONY TIME
Testimony Time
The gentleman is here in our midst right now to share the incredible testimony
of what Jesus Christ has done in his life, completely restoring him through
that touch of the Holy Spirit.
Right now we want to listen to him and give glory to God for everything He has done.
We can see the emotion he is displaying right now, considering where he is coming from
and what God Almighty has done for him and remove that burden and pain.
Brother, you are very welcome in Jesus' name.
Please introduce yourself to us, tell us your name and the lady standing beside you.
Praise the Lord!
People of God, I want you to say that 'hallelujah' louder than this
because I am the most happiest person standing here today.
Praise the Lord!
Amen.
My name is Mr Friday Igbaifua. I come from Edo State, Nigeria.
I am 35 years old.
I came to give my testimony for the glory of God.
The lady standing here with me is my mother.
It was unfortunate.
One day, I went for the whole day, looking for a job. I am a professional truck driver.
Throughout that day, I really needed the toilet as I was feeling sick in my stomach.
I didn't understand.
I decided to look for a toilet.
At the toilet, I realised nothing came out but gas kept coming out of me.
I said, okay.
I stood up and because I could not go to the toilet, I decided to wear my trousers and go.
When I tried to clean myself up, I could feel something in my buttocks - the anus came out.
I wondered what this was and thought that I was going to die that day.
There was nobody to help me.
Later on, around 9 -10 o'clock in the evening, I struggled to put my clothes back on
and I would have entered a vehicle to go home.
Because of the thing that came out of my anus, I could not stop any vehicle or motorbike;
I had to struggle to trek from Tin-Can Island to Surulere to make sure that I got home.
I reached home at 2 o'clock in the morning.
I struggled to knock the door and my mother came out and asked why I came at a very late hour,
that I had not come home that late.
I explained to her and I pulled down my trousers and showed her my condition.
My mummy saw it and shouted, "Jesus! What is this?"
She said that this had never happened to any of her children and asked where it came from.
I said, "I didn't know".
She now said I should be patient until daybreak.
Then, we tried to look for a solution to that anus cancer.
She started calling some of her friends who asked her to take me to a hospital.
We rushed to the hospital.
When the doctor saw the anus cancer, he said that there was no solution to that problem but surgery.
My mother refused to take the doctor's suggestion to cut it off.
She said that I should remain alive as this was not her child's portion.
She started calling her relations, colleagues and friends
who later advised her to take me to a herbalist or a native doctor.
He may find a solution to anus cancer.
I decided to follow my mother to a herbalist and the woman said that she was going to do it.
My mother left me with the woman for almost five days.
The woman kept giving me different kinds of concoctions and forcing me to drink them.
She was putting things on the surface of the cancer and I thought I would die there.
The day my mummy came back, I told her that I wanted to follow her back home.
With all the pain, I decided it was better for me to stay at home.
The pain would not allow me to rest. Since that day, I could not sleep.
Sleep would never come, talkless of sitting down.
I would just lie down and say, "God, is this how people used to die?"
I said, "God, let me die once and for all instead of dying gradually."
But I still had faith and when I looked at the cancer through a mirror, I continued praying.
It was a few days ago when the pain was so much that I called my mum to take me to the hospital.
I said that if they wanted to cut off the cancer, they should cut it off because of the pain.
My mum agreed and when we got to the hospital, we met a lot of people there.
They were attending to them one by one but because of the pain, I had to lie on the floor.
I kept on crying, rolling on the ground when suddenly an elderly man appeared to me.
He asked me what the problem was and I told him that it was anus cancer.
He said that they should take me to The SCOAN.
Mr Friday Matthew Igbaifua & Mother - Healed of Anus Cancer in Jesus' Name
I asked what The SCOAN was and whether it was a hospital.
The man answered that it was not a hospital but that a prophet would pray for me and
when he did, the cancer would be removed.
Mr Friday Matthew Igbaifua & Mother - Healed of Anus Cancer in Jesus' Name
I hope we all understand what our brother is saying.
As he was lying in agony on the floor of the hospital, actually hoping to get an operation
to remove that cancer coming out of his anus, an elderly man saw his condition
and advised him that he must come to The SCOAN.
That was actually in the hospital where he was preparing to undergo an operation.
Brother, just before you talk about coming here.
Can you just describe for the benefit of those here the pain you were in at that period.
Just try and describe that pain and how severe it was.
That pain was as if someone had died.
Someone who could not sleep. I could not sit down, talkless of standing.
It was like I was dead. It was a seriously terrible pain that I had never experienced in my life
or even seen in another person's life.
When we came to The SCOAN and the ushers saw my situation,
they even left the other people and started attending to my mum and I.
My mum told me that I was lucky as those people were attending to me.
They were running here and there.
Then, the pastor came out to start the ministration on that service day.
The usher now brought us to where the pastor would minister to me.
When I saw the pastor, I was wondering because I had been hearing about
T. B. Joshua but I had never heard about The SCOAN.
I now said, okay.
Since they said I should come to The SCOAN and it is prayer, God can heal me. I will receive my healing here.
That was what I believed in my mind.
As the man of God came out, I saw him praying and by the time he touched me,
I first of all thought, "What is this touch going to do in me?"
At the second touch, I said, "No" and at the third touch, I felt in my stomach
that they wanted to draw my anus inside.
It was like the anus cancer was forcing itself to go inside.
I was praying, "Go inside, in Jesus' name!" Then I said, "Thank You, Jesus. I am free".
I had that belief that I was free.
They gave me three bottles of Morning Water and said that I should drink one and
minister the other ones on the surface of the anus cancer.
When I got home, I prayed, "Let the Morning Water turn to the blood of Jesus
and wash out every disease and sickness from my stomach, in Jesus' name".
That's when I opened that Morning Water. I drank one and finished it.
I opened the other one. I now spoke to that one too and said,
"Since this is also water, let it be the blood of Jesus.
When I sprinkle the surface, let it wash all the sickness and every disease".
I kept on spraying the surface, spraying on it.
That night, I kept on spraying it before I slept.
It was that night, I went to the toilet like I never had in my life.
I went to the toilet and defaecated everything out of my stomach.
I then called my mummy and said, "Mummy, come and see the toilet!"
"Look at it; come and see!"
My mummy said, "What is this!"
I said, "Come and see!"
The toilet was filled up.
When I wanted to go to the toilet before, this is how I would do it.
I would be shouting but faeces would not drop out.
I would be eating frequently but I never defaecated since that day.
The day I drank that Morning Water, my brother, my sister,
I'm saying, it's like the toilet wanted to fill up.
The following morning, I went to the toilet again and I was not having pain. My body was free.
The anus cancer was still there but there was no pain.
I could not even sit down before, I always had to lie down.
But that following day, I sat on one side first.
I could not sit on one side before, I always had to lie down.
I was tired of lying down. I said that since this man of God has touched me
and given me the Morning Water, I believe my life had changed and I was healed.
It was last week I came back to The SCOAN and told the ushers that the cancer was disappearing.
They asked me if I was sure and I said yes, so they interviewed me.
They asked me to open the place and truly the cancer had gone so they said I should tap it.
When I tapped it, they said I should come today to give my testimony for the glory of God.
Brother, you mean to say that it was after this prayer, as you ministered the Morning Water
given to you in the church, you realised that first of all, the pain disappeared and then
the growth that was coming out of your anus actually shot back inside and completely disappeared.
When I used the last Morning Water, it drew the cancer inside.
I thought that maybe the cancer had come out again, but I checked and it was not there.
I ran to show my mum and she said, "God has done it! Praise the Lord!"
Let's put our hands together for Jesus Christ!
So brother, as you are standing here right now, you are completely restored
and you can do everything that you were not able to do before?
I'm the strongest man standing here right now!
Mr Friday Matthew Igbaifua & Mother - Healed of Anus Cancer in Jesus' Name
I was someone that if I wanted to sit down before, I would do it like this.
The day they brought me to the church, this is how I was doing it.
By the time the pain would be too much, I would change my position.
I would be dodging the face of the cancer.
I would sit like this and say, "God, I'm going to die here!"
But look at me today, can't you see that I'm a free man?
Mr Friday Matthew Igbaifua & Mother - Healed of Anus Cancer in Jesus' Name
Glory be to Jesus Christ! And you said before, brother, you could even barely walk.
Just demonstrate how you were moving before and how you can now move.
Before, I would put my hand on the knickers, shift it to prevent it from touching
the surface of the cancer so that it would not wound me.
Then, I would walk like this.
Mr Friday Matthew Igbaifua & Mother - Healed of Anus Cancer in Jesus' Name
But right now?
Right now, see how I have put on my trousers.
Do you want me to run?
Mr Friday Matthew Igbaifua & Mother - Healed of Anus Cancer in Jesus' Name
I give praise to God Almighty!
Amen. People of God, let's put our hands together for Jesus Christ!
Who else could do this but our Lord Jesus Christ.
This was the brother that was at the point of death because of the severity of the pain.
The medical doctors actually wanted to operate but as he was lying in pain
on the hospital floor, someone directed him to The SCOAN. And just receiving that touch,
that prayer in the power of the Holy Spirit, the pain disappeared, the growth started reducing
and then completely shot inside and today he is restored and free to the glory of God.
One more time, let's put our hands together for Jesus Christ!
What is your word of advice to our viewers all over the world and those who are present here?
My advice to viewers all over the world and those watching me here
is that anyone who has a problem like this should still have faith and hope.
Believe that Jesus heals all manner of sickness and disease.
Jesus heals so you should have the faith that the Lord can heal anyone.
Amen. Let's put our hands together for Jesus Christ one more time.
Finally, let's just hear a quick word from your mother as well.
Madam, you are welcome, in Jesus' name.
What can you say about what Jesus Christ has done in the life of your son?
Praise the Lord!
Praise Master Jesus!
I'm coming here today to share my testimony! I give glory to God!
Mr Friday Matthew Igbaifua & Mother - Healed of Anus Cancer in Jesus' Name
This is just our mother's way of expressing her appreciation to God,
knowing that He has really rescued her son's life from the jaws of death.
We thank God for your life, mama. So what can you say about what Jesus has done for your son?
I thank the God of T. B. Joshua that delivered my son.
My son has said everything! I give glory to God, in Jesus' name!
Amen. Let's put our hands together for Jesus Christ.
So we thank God for what God has done in this family and we pray that God will give you
the grace to continue to make the Word of God the standard for your life
and we know that the best is yet to come as you do so, in Jesus' name.
Mr Friday Matthew Igbaifua & Mother - Healed of Anus Cancer in Jesus' Name
RV: Mel Flowers 13/04/2019